# WorldQuiz
This is about a quiz of the world geography

 //////////copy from here //////////



            Array.append(Question(questionText: "Russia is the largest country in the world ", answer: true))

            Array.append(Question(questionText: "Antartica is near the north Pole ", answer: false))

             Array.append(Question(questionText: "Mariana trenches is the deepest point on earth", answer: true))

              Array.append(Question(questionText: "Core of the earth is hotter than the surface of the Sun.", answer: true))

             Array.append(Question(questionText: " the population of earth is over 7 billion", answer: true))

            Array.append(Question(questionText: "The earth was formed over 14 billion years ago", answer: false))

              Array.append(Question(questionText: "Jupiter the largest planet in the solar system, has no solid surface to land upon", answer: true))

         Array.append(Question(questionText: "Over 30% of earth water bodies are consist of fresh water", answer: false))

         Array.append(Question(questionText: "Earth was formed 4.5 billion year ago", answer: true))

          Array.append(Question(questionText: "It is believed that 70% of space is filled with Dark energy which cannot be measured by modern equipments", answer: true))

             Array.append(Question(questionText: "Earth is a perfect round body of mass ", answer: false))

            Array.append(Question(questionText: "Amazon river is the longest river on the planet", answer: false))

             Array.append(Question(questionText: "Its takes light from Sun, over 8 minutes to traverse the space and reach Earth ", answer: true))
